akari ga oreba kage ga dekiru to itta
You said if there's light, there are shadow
ano hi no kimi no koe ga wasure rarezu ni
I can't forget the words you said that day
tsuyoku aritai to negai
I wish to be strong
rousoku wo keshita yubi
I put out the candle with my finger
hi no watsusa ni inochi wo oboete
The heat of the flames reminded me of life
boku no koa ga hajikeru
The core of my being bursts open
guren no ai ga kokoro wo yaite
This red-hot love burns my heart
kaze ni mayoe ba namida ga ochiru
While wandering in the wind, tears start to fall
kizutsuki nagara mirai shinjite
Though I'm hurt, I believe in the future
mata saki e sono saki e
Let's go further and further ahead
gareki no sora wa bokura no kizuna
The rubble in the sky is our bond
osou mayakashi kechirashite yaru
I'll cut through the attempts to deceive me
tatakai no hate ni nani mo nakutemo
Even if there's nothing at the end of the battle
mata saki e sono saki e Ikou
Let's go further and further ahead
Kakashi: Shadow of the Anbu
Coup D'état
（カカシ）暗部に入ったからには→
You're part of the ANBU now and
お前も　この任務は
避けて通れない。
this is one mission
you cannot avoid.
（イタチ）ここでは何の任務を？
What kind of mission is this?
６年前　九尾事件のとき→
When the Nine Tails incident
occurred six years ago,
上層部は　うちは一族の仕業ではと
疑いを持った。
the higher-ups suspected
the Uchiha Clan was behind it.
以来　うちは地区の２４時間監視が
始まったのさ。
Since then, the Uchiha district has been
under 24-hour surveillance.
((三代目火影様　九尾が…。
Lord Third! The Nine Tails!
九尾が急に里に出現しました。
The Nine Tails has suddenly
appeared in the Village!
わかっておる。
あれは　わしがおさえる。
I'm aware of that!
I will suppress it.
お前たちは非戦闘員の
保護に回るのじゃ。
You and the others,
protect the civilians!
はっ！
Yes, sir!
（ダンゾウ）うちはの警務部隊に
非戦闘員を保護させよ。
You should have ordered the Uchiha
Police Force to guard the civilians
後方に待機させるべきだ。
and kept them in the rear.
うちは一族の瞳術は
九尾をおさえるのに使えるのだ。
We can use the Visual Prowess of
the Uchiha to suppress the Nine Tails!
九尾を操るのにも使えるのだ。
They can also manipulate
the Nine Tails!
もしヤツらが九尾を手なずけ→
If they take control of the Nine Tails,
and use it to their advantage,
そのまま自分たちの力としたら→
うちはマダラの再来となろう。
it will be like the second coming
of Madara Uchiha.
非戦闘員の保護は
おぬしに任せる。
I will leave you to
protect the civilians.
暗部　警務部隊　好きに使うがよい。
Order the ANBU and
security units as you wish.
里の若者たちも保護対象とせよ。
Guard the village youth as well.
了解した。
Understood.
こっちだ　急げ！
This way, hurry!
落ち着いて！
ここは大丈夫だ！
Calm down!
You're safe here.
隊長
我々も援軍に向かいましょう。
Captain, we should go and assist.
（フガク）警務部隊は
非戦闘員を保護する。
The Police Force will guard
the civilians.
しかし　隊長！
But Captain...!
それが里からの命令だ。
That's the order from the Village.
あっちか！？
It's over there!
（イタチ）よしよし
ビックリしちゃったな。
There, there. You're scared, huh?
今のうちだ　避難所に急ぐよ。
Now's our chance.
Let's get you to safety.
このたびの九尾事件
わからぬことが多すぎる。
There are too many
unanswered questions
surrounding this recent
Nine Tails incident.
クシナの封印が
解けたのかと思ったが→
I thought that Kushina's seal
had been broken.
それでは　ビワコや暗部たちが
殺された理由がつかぬ。
But that doesn't explain why Biwako
and the ANBU were killed.
誰か犯人が
いるというわけだな。
Which means someone is behind this.
（ダンゾウ）うちはの者ではないのか？
Like someone from the Uchiha?
根拠は？
Why do you say that?
九尾をただ解放しても
暴走するだけだ。
Even if the Nine Tails broke free,
it would have just gone wild.
コントロールできる用意がなければ
事件など起こせぬ。
Without someone to control it,
it couldn't have caused this incident.
そこで写輪眼か…。
Hence, the Sharingan...
うちはの瞳術なら
九尾を操れるというしな。
The Uchiha can control the Nine Tails
with their Visual Prowess...
しかし　目的は？
But for what purpose?
（ダンゾウ）木ノ葉における
うちはの復権。
To regain their position of power
within the Hidden Leaf Village.
なるほどな。
I see...
だがそれは推測にすぎぬ。
That's just conjecture.
今後は　うちは一族の監視を
強化せねば。
We must increase our surveillance
of the Uchiha.
うちは地区を２４時間
監視体制に置くのだ。
We must keep them
under 24-hour watch.
それでは余計な反発を招く。
That's bound to
incite them unnecessarily!
秘密裏に暗部にやらせればよい。
Let the ANBU do it secretly.
用心にこしたことはないな。
うむ。
Better to be safe than sorry.
待て！
Wait!
うちはの仕業と
わかったわけではない。
We don't know if the Uchiha
are responsible for this.
わからぬから　やるのだ。
That's precisely why
this is necessary.
何も出なければ
むしろ　それが　うちはのためだ。
And if nothing comes out of it...
it will be to the Uchiha's benefit.
HIDDEN LEAF HOSPITAL
(（ミコト）クシナ…))
Kushina...
交代だ。
Time to switch.
異常なしです。
ここが？
Nothing to report.
監視所は　ここだけじゃないぜ。
This is...
This isn't the only
surveillance center around.
ダンゾウ様の暗部も見張っている。
Lord Danzo's ANBU are
also watching them.
どうする？　仲間に
このことを伝えにいくか？
Now what'll you do?
Notify your clan about this?
ここでの俺の仕事は？
What is my job here?
そいつで　ずっと覗いてな。
Just keep watching through that.
それじゃ　隊長
俺たちはこれで。
Okay, Captain. We're going.
しっかり見張れよ　イタチ。
Stay alert, Itachi.
暗部には　こんな仕事もある。
This is part of our job as ANBU.
暗殺とは違うが　まぁ
汚れ仕事には変わりはない。
It's not assassination
but it's still dirty work.
任務は任務です。
A mission is a mission.
お前の場合　自分の仲間や家族を
監視するんだから　よけいにだ。
You'll be spying on your friends
and family. It's even dirtier.
シフトを変えてやってもいいが。
I can take this shift,
if you want.
構いません　それに…。
No, that's not necessary.
Besides...
それに？
Besides?
里に疑いをもたれていることは→
The Uchiha Clan is aware
that they're under suspicion.
うちは一族のほうでも
感じています。
（カカシ）そうだろうな。
I guess you would be.
いいかげんにしろよ！
Go to hell!
何すんだよ　こら！
だいたい　あのとき　お前がな！
What the hell was that for?!
You're the one that...
お前が悪いんだろ！
It's your fault.
俺じゃねえよ　お前だ！
ちょっと　やめなさいよ！
- It wasn't me!
- Sure, it was!
Hey, stop that!
おい　何の騒ぎだ！
Hey, what's going on?!
おとなしくしろ！
Calm down!
Why you...!
警務部隊なんか
お呼びじゃねえよ！
Who needs the Police Force?!
九尾のときみたいに隠れてろ！
なんだと　この！
Just go and hide like you did
with the Nine Tails!
What did you say?
イテテテ！
２人とも連行する！
Ow ow ow!
We're taking you both into custody!
離せよ！
いいから黙って歩け！
Let me go!
Be quiet and walk!
酔っ払いのケンカだろ？
It was just a drunken argument...
仲裁でいいものを。
Couldn't they just
stop the fighting?
警務部隊の取り締まりが→
Complaints about harsh treatment
by the Police Force are on the rise.
厳しくなったと
苦情が増えておる。
部隊に対して
不信感が募っているようだ。
People have started
to distrust them.
うちはが
増長しているようだな。
The Uchiha are growing impudent.
いや　反発であろう。
No, it's backlash.
６年前の九尾事件が
尾を引いておるのだ。
The negativity from the Nine Tails' incident
six years ago still hangs over them.
あのとき　うちはの者は
被害にあっておらんだろうに。
The Uchiha didn't suffer
any damage that time.
それが不信感のもとということか。
That is the cause of suspicion...
そして　九尾から
うちはを遠のけたことは→
Furthermore, the Uchiha viewed
our distancing them from the Nine Tails
うちはの側にも
木ノ葉から疑われているという→
as a sign of
the Hidden Leaf's distrust.
不信感を生んでしまったようだ。
うちはの隔離政策は
二代目様から続く→
Our strategy of isolating the Uchiha
is a fundamental policy of the Leaf
木ノ葉の基本方針。
なにを今さら。
put in place by Lord Second.
Why are they raising a fuss
after all this time?
二代目様の意図は隔離ではない。
各一族への配慮だ。
The Lord Second's intention
wasn't isolation.
He was just concerned for each clan.
わしらの友であった
うちはカガミを忘れたか。
Have you forgotten about
our friend Kagami Uchiha?
忘れなどせぬ。　あやつの
瞳術には何度も助けられた。
I haven't forgotten.
He saved me many times
with his Visual Jutsu.
うちは一族は木ノ葉の仲間だ。
The Uchiha Clan is
a friend of the Hidden Leaf.
仲間として
とめておかねばならぬ。
We must ensure
they stay that way.
とめておけるものならばな。
If we can...
うわ～っ！
落ち着け！
幻術…　いつの間に！？
Calm down!
A genjutsu!
But when did that happen?
白眼！
Byakugan!
撤退する！
しかし　隊長！
We're retreating!
But Captain...!
あれは木ノ葉の瞬身　うちはシスイだ。
It's Shisui Uchiha,
the Teleporter of the Leaf.
これでは相手にならぬ　引くぞ！
We're no match for him. Retreat!
（シスイ）これで霧隠れも　しばらくは
おとなしくなるだろう。
That should keep the Hidden Mist
quiet for a while.
シスイ隊　任務完了。
帰還しました。
Team Shisui has returned and
our mission was successfully completed.
そうか
長期の任務ご苦労であったな。
That was a long mission.
Thank you for your hard work.
しばし　休暇をとるがよい。
Go and rest.
でしたら　三代目にお願いが。
I have a request, Lord Third.
ん？
うちは一族と里の間の不信感に
心を痛めています。
I'm very troubled by the suspicion
cast upon the Uchiha Clan.
うむ　わしもじゃ。
So am I.
一族と里を　再び信頼で→
I'm hoping that
my clan and the Village
繋ぐことができればと
思っています。
will be able to trust
each other again.
その任務を
授けてもらえないでしょうか？
Will you assign this mission to me?
通常任務から
外してほしいということか？
Do you want to be released
from your regular duties?
はい。　それと俺にある程度の
権限を与えてください。
Yes. And I'd like to be given
a certain amount of authority.
わかった。　お前にはわしから→
All right. Let's say I ordered you on
a top-secret investigative mission.
極秘の調査任務を出した
ということにする。
何か不備が生じたときは
わしの名を出せ。
If anyone objects, tell them my name,
責任はすべて　わしがとる。
and I will take full responsibility.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you.
お前を見ていると
わしのかつての友→
You remind me so much
of my old friend, Kagami Uchiha.
うちはカガミを思い出す。
まだまだ及びません。
I am nowhere near his caliber.
（サスケ）兄さん！　任務　終わったの？
Big Brother!
Are you done with your mission?
だったら
俺の修業につきあってよ。
If you are, help me train!
許せサスケ　急な呼び出しだ。
Sorry, Sasuke.
I have an urgent summons.
昔よく　ここで遊んだな。
（イタチ）戻っていたのか？
We played here a lot.
So you were back.
ああ　ようやく
霧隠れを追っ払えたよ。
Yeah. We finally chased
the Hidden Mist away.
用件は？
Why did you want to see me?
お前の率直な意見を聞きたい。
I want to hear
your honest opinion.
フガクさんは　どこまで
本気だと思う？
How serious do you think Fugaku is?
本気とは？
What do you mean by serious?
クーデターだ。
A coup d'état.
うちはには
里に対する不満が高まっている。
Dissatisfaction towards the Village
is growing among the Uchiha.
里がこのままなら　うちはも
我慢の限界を超えるだろう。
If the Village doesn't change,
the Uchiha won't stand for it anymore.
里が変われば　うちはも変わるか。
If the Village changes,
so will the Uchiha.
だが　うちはが変わらなければ
里は変わらない。
But if the Uchiha doesn't change,
neither will the Village.
双方に不信感がある以上
事態は悪化するだけだ。
As long as the two sides
distrust each other,
things will only get worse.
俺は　その不信を払いたい。
I want to clear up that suspicion.
できると思うか？
You think you can?
さあな。　しかし　やらねば。
I don't know, but I have to try...
うちはが　クーデターを起こせば→
If the Uchiha attempts a coup d'état,
it will bode badly for both sides.
それは双方にとって
不幸な結果しかもたらさない。
俺もクーデターには反対だ。
I'm against a coup d'état as well.
しかし　阻止するには
よほどのことをしなければ。
But it will take something big
to stop it.
わかっている。
だがお前は動かないほうがいい。
I know.
But you shouldn't do anything.
なぜだ？
Why's that?
Some members on the Police Force
are suspicious of you...
警務部隊の一部が
お前を疑っている。
俺にお前の監視を命じてきた。
and I've been ordered
to spy on you.
（フガク）なんだと？
What?!
明日がどんな日か
お前も知っているだろう。
Do you know what day tomorrow is?!
お前は
自分の立場がわかっていない。
You don't understand
your own position!
俺は明日　任務につく。
I'm setting out on
a mission tomorrow.
何の任務だ？
What kind of mission?
それは言えない。　極秘任務だ。
I can't tell you...
It's top-secret.
イタチ　お前は一族と里の中枢を繋ぐ
パイプ役でもあるのだ。
Itachi... You also serve as
the Uchiha Clan's pipeline
to the Village nerve center.
それは　わかってるな？
You know that, don't you?
ああ。
Yes...
それをよく肝に銘じておけ。
Bear that in mind.
そして　明日の会合には来い。
And come to tomorrow's assembly!
（ダンゾウ）今夜は　うちはが
また会合を持つそうだ。
The Uchiha are assembling
again tonight.
会合のことは　わしも知っておる。
I know about it as well.
だが　うちは一族の祭事
と言われては口がはさめぬ。
But we cannot interfere
with their clan rituals.
Rituals indeed!
何が祭事だ！
They're going to fan the flames
of distrust against us,
里に対する反目を高め
その敵対心を利用して→
一族の結束を
はかろうというのだろう。
then use it to unite the clan.
これは　クーデターの準備だ。
They are preparing for a coup d'état.
その芽は摘むことにする。　シスイ。
And the one to nip it
in the bud is...
Shisui!
（ダンゾウ）うちはシスイ？
Shisui Uchiha?
シスイが　その会合に出る。
Shisui will attend the assembly.
And if Fugaku Uchiha incites
a rebellion...
そして　もし　うちはフガクが
クーデターを企んでおったなら…。
別天神を使います。
I will use my Kotoamatsukami.
お前の瞳術か。
Your Visual Jutsu...
相手に気づかれることなく→
He will have no clue that Shisui
is controlling his actions.
己の意思で動いているかのように
操るという。
He will believe that
his words are his own.
フガクさんに里との共存を
考えてもらいます。
I'm going to make Fugaku think
about co-existence with the Village.
フガク一人を改心させて
うちはの不満が収まるとも思えぬ。
I don't think that
controlling only Fugaku
will put an end to
the Uchiha's dissatisfaction.
いや
うちはが変わるというのなら→
No. If the Uchiha will change,
then we of the Leaf must change too.
わしらも変わればよい。
うちはの待遇を改善していこう。
Let us improve our relations
with the Uchiha.
それが　俺の願いです。
That is my hope.
暗部を一人
後方支援につけておく。
I will assign one ANBU
behind the scenes.
頼むぞ　シスイ。
I'm counting on you, Shisui.
Yes, sir!
はっ！
（ミコト）来ませんね。　イタチ。
Itachi isn't coming, is he?
《遅いな》
He's late.
なんでしょうか？　ダンゾウ様。
What is it, Lord Danzo?
It's almost time for
the assembly to start.
そろそろ
会合の時間なのですが…。
フガクに瞳術をかけ
うちはをまとめたとて→
Even if you use your Visual Jutsu
on Fugaku to get the clan to cooperate,
里が変わらなければ　どうする？
what if the Village doesn't change?
火影様が変えてくれると
約束してくれました。
Lord Hokage has promised
to make it change.
三代目が説得しても
里の者の不信はそうそう消えぬぞ。
Even if Lord Third is satisfied,
the distrust among
the Leaf will not go away.
わかっています。
I realize that. But in time...
ですが　時間をかけていけば…。
それにだ→
Besides, someone who's always suspicious
like me will never change.
わしのような疑り深い者も
そう簡単には考えを変えぬ。
そのときは　どうする？
しかし　ダンゾウ様…。
What will you do then?
But Lord Danzo...
そのときには　このわしにも→
When the time comes,
will you use your Kotoamatsukami
on me too?
別天神とやらを
使うのか？
俺は…。
その写輪眼　わしが預かる。
I'm...
Your Sharingan...
shall be in my safekeeping!
御免！
Forgive me.
ただの幻術です。
じきに覚めるでしょう。
It's only genjutsu...
You'll snap out of it shortly.
あっ！　写輪眼！？
Sharingan?!
この眼のかわりにいただくぞ。
I'm going to take it
to replace this eye.
もう片方も渡してもらおう。
Give me the other one too.
《火遁　豪火球の術！》
Fire Style! Fireball Jutsu!
水遁　水乱波！
Water Style! Raging Waves!
瞬身の術か！
追え！
It's a Teleportation Jutsu!
Go after him.
シスイか？
Is that you, Shisui?
Come with me.
（シスイ）来い！
もう　うちはのクーデターは
止められそうにない。
It's too late to stop
the coup d'état by the Uchiha.
このまま木ノ葉が
内戦を起こせば→
If civil war breaks out
in the Leaf Village,
他国が必ず攻め入ってくる。
other nations are sure
to attack...
which means a full-scale war.
まず　戦争になる。
I was going to try to stop
the coup d'état with Kotoamatsukami, but...
別天神を使い
クーデターを止めようとした矢先→
ダンゾウに右眼を奪われた。
Lord Danzo took my right eye...
ヤツは　俺を信用していない。
He doesn't trust me.
He intends to protect
the Village his own way,
なりふり構うことなく
自分のやり方で里を守るつもりだ。
no matter what it takes
or how it looks.
恐らく　左眼も狙われる。
I suspect he'll come after
my left eye as well.
So I want to give it to you
before he has a chance.
その前に　この眼は　お前に渡す。
《シスイ…》
Shisui.
You're the only person I can count on,
my best friend.
頼めるのは　親友のお前だけだ。
この里を…
うちはの名を守ってくれ。
Please protect this Village...
and the honor of the Uchiha name.
確かに受け取ったぞ。
お前は　どうするんだ？
I accept it.
What will you do now?
俺が死ねば
いくつも状況が変わるだろう。
If I die, several circumstances
will change.
遺書ものこしてきた。
待て　シスイ！
I've left behind a note already...
Wait, Shisui!
Don't stop me, Itachi.
止めるなよ　イタチ！
俺の友ならば。
If you're my friend...
シスイ！！
Shisui!
シスイ…。
Shisui...
うっ！　俺が何したってんだよ！
Oww! What are you accusing me of?!
いいから　おとなしくしろ。
Just be quiet!
Don't be so rough.
（フガク）手荒な真似はやめろ。
隊長。
Captain...
あなたには
容疑がかけられている。
You are a suspect...
and you're coming to
Headquarters with us.
本部まで同行願おう。
お…　おう。
F-Fine...
Remember to follow
our investigative procedures!
いいか　捜査手順は順守しろ。
はっ！
Yes, sir!
ほら　歩け！
C'mon, move.
（イタチ）うちはシスイは　一族において→
Shisui Uchiha was a core member
of the Uchiha.
若手の中核を担う人物。
その彼の自殺により→
His suicide demoralized and
lessened their fighting power all at once.
うちはの士気も戦力も
一気に落ちてしまいました。
結果的に反乱の芽は摘んだか。
So the coup d'état has been foiled.
シスイも　己の命を投げ出さねば→
Are you saying
there was no other way
but for Shisui to give his life?
止めようがなかったというのか。
I shouldn't have pushed him...
わしが　無理をさせてしまったか。
There are a few among the Uchiha
うちはの中に　お前が　シスイを
殺したと疑う者がいるようだが。
who believe that you killed Shisui.
俺もシスイも同じく　うちはのことを
考えて働いていた。
The ones who believe that
did not know
that Shisui and I were working
towards the same goal.
それを知らない連中の
言うことです。
Shisui did not appear at
our rendezvous point.
（イタチ）シスイは　合流地点に
現れませんでした。
秘密があるゆえに疑われたか。
He had secrets,
so he was suspected.
暗部から　正式に自殺だと
伝えておこう。
I will notify the ANBU that
it was officially a suicide.
よいな　ヒルゼン。
うむ。
Agreed, Hiruzen?
あっ！
うわっ！
あっ！　それは雷切。
That's the Lightning Blade!
You're... the Copy Ninja of the Leaf!
キサマ　木ノ葉のコピー忍者…。
カカシ…。
Kaka... shi...
You've become quite well known.
（テンゾウ）先輩の名前も　ずいぶんと
広まっちゃいましたね。
長年やってりゃ有名にもならぁ。
Do it long enough and
you're bound to become famous.
Clear the area.
現場を処理しろ
木ノ葉の痕跡は　一切残すなよ。
Leave no trace of the Hidden Leaf.
へいへい　わかってますよ。
Yeah, yeah. I know.
Dirty work is part of
the ANBU's modus operandi.
暗部の任務に
汚れ仕事はつきものですから。
隊長の写輪眼は　友から託されたと
言ってましたね。
You said that a friend gave
your Sharingan to you.
その思いとともにな。
Along with a wish.
その思いには
応えねばなりませんか？
Do you need to honor that wish?
Yes, I intend to.
ああ　俺はそのつもりでいる。
I know about
the Shisui Uchiha incident.
うちはシスイの件は
俺も知っている。
それの何かか？
Is it about that?
No, I'm fine.
いえ　大丈夫です。
そうか。
I see...
Anyway, there's not a lot I can do,
but let me know if there's anything.
ま　たいしたことはできないが
何かあったら言ってくれ。
Yes.
はい。
((頼めるのは　親友のお前だけだ。
You're the only person I can count on,
my best friend.
Please protect this Village...
and the honor of the Uchiha name.
(この里を…
うちはの名を守ってくれ))
《シスイ　あれから状況は
更に悪くなった。
Shisui.
Things have gotten much worse
since then.
俺は　両方は守れそうにない》
I don't think
I can protect everyone.
kidzuite ndaro sou sekai ga kataru itsuwari to
I'm sure you've realized by now that the world tells lies
amai wana ni soko ni wa hontou nante nai koto o
And lays alluring traps, but there's no truth behind them
riyuu sagashite run away why? sono mewotojiteru no?
Search for a reason Run away Why?
Why are you closing your eyes?
tell me why can't you
Tell me why can't you
shinjitsu ni te o nobase!
Reach out for the truth!
always (sakebe shout out) all time (tsukame catch up)
Always (Scream, Shout out)
All the time (Catch it, Catch up)
everybody knows (we are the seeker get fire!!!)
Everybody knows (We are the seeker Get fire!!!)
moyase moyase kokoro no honou
Burn, burn the fire in your heart
tsuyoku aritai to negau nonaraba
if you firmly wish for it
narase narase mezame no kane o
Ring, ring the bell of awakening
koyoi tsuki no shita de kokoro sakebe
Shout from your heart under the moon tonight
utae utae hoero hoero
Sing, sing, howl, howl,
kibou no hikari o nozomu nonaraba
if you want the light of hope
moyase moyase kokoro no honou
Burn, burn the fire in your heart
akai tsuki no shita de kimi o sakebe
Shout to you under the red moon
ima ima ima flame up (catch the fire)
Now, now, now, Flame up (Catch the fire)
ima ima ima flame up (blaze up!!!)
Now, now, now, Flame up (Blaze up!!!)
It seems someone has been
infiltrating the Village recently.
The only thing we can do is
to ask the Police Force
to step up their patrols.
＜　きょうから１３代目＞
What happened?
I went to the Uchiha District
for the first time in a long time.
＜旬の野菜が大好きな豆助＞
It felt like they didn't want
any outsiders there.
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Night of the Tragedy"
≫豆助
I see...
きょうのお野菜は
今が旬のアレよ？
＜　その野菜とは…？＞